bzfilm.com 2017-06-08

# Privacy Policy

First of all, thanks again for stopping by – we appreciate every reader. Our privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at “BZFilm.com”.

Make sure you read it all, before submitting any of your personal information. By using “BZFilm.com”, you are accepting the practices described in our privacy policy. **The policy may be changed, however, the page will be immediately updated once the changes are applied.**

Any user/reader is encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever he/she visits “BZFilm.com” to make sure how the provided personal information will be used.

**Keep in mind: Privacy policy described here is for “BZFilm.com” website only.**

_**Collection of Information**_  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, and email addresses when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

_**Cookie/Tracking**_  
“BZFilm.com” uses cookies, which eventually help us improve your access to our website and identify the returning to “BZFilm.com”. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on “BZFilm.com”.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on “BZFilm.com” (advertisers, for example). However, “BZFilm.com” does not have any access to or control over these cookies. We do share some aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers, however, this is in no way linked to any personal information you might have provided us, that could identify any individual person.

_**Links**_  
“BZFilm.com” contains links to other websites. Please, be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our readers to be aware when they leave “BZFilm.com” and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information.

_**Information distribution**_  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

_**Privacy Contact Information**_  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments, [you can always reach us here](http://bzfilm.com/contact/).

_**Refund policy**_

By purchasing our services (advertising in the form of banners, text links, articles), you indicate that you have read and agree with our Privacy and Advertising policies.

Since BZFilm.com offers non-tangible digital goods, we will not be able to “return” or refund the service you purchased.

Please, make sure you ask everything you need regarding BZFilm’s advertising services before you make a purchase. If you are having any issues with purchased service, make sure you [contact us](http://bzfilm.com/contact/), and we will do our best to resolve the problem.

* * *

* * *

Never miss an article again!

* * *
